<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on トリ</title><link>http://example.org/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on トリ</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Low power home server without a RaspberryPi</title><link>http://example.org/posts/low-power-home-server-with-a-pi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/low-power-home-server-with-a-pi/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s face it electricity is expensive, in the UK alone the cost per kWh has doubled over the last year, and reflecting on what we&amp;rsquo;re running in our homes 24/7 like home servers feels like problem worthy of attention.
Where we begin As it stood in my home, Frigate (CCTV NVR), Home Assiatant (Home Automation), Plex (Media Server) &amp;amp; NAS were all running from a HP ProLiant DL380p Gen8. At the time I aquired this server it provided a rock solid base to run everything from, and be dammed the power consumption electricy was cheap.</description></item><item><title>Sorting colors</title><link>http://example.org/posts/sorting-colors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/sorting-colors/</guid><description>Previously i talked about finding similar colors, I&amp;rsquo;d now like to move onto sorting.
given a sparse set of colors how do i arrange them in an aesthetically pleasing order. There is an inherent problem with this statement through. I have two axis in which I can work on screen x and y, but color is three dimensional. So we have to work out a way to minimise one of those axis or combine two to achieve something close to a pleasant lay down.</description></item><item><title>Finding similar colors</title><link>http://example.org/posts/finding-similar-colors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/finding-similar-colors/</guid><description>Every once in a while I find a subject I get obsessed with. At the moment it&amp;rsquo;s color, so for the next few posts I want to document some of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with. Starting at the beginning&amp;hellip;
given any x,y point in a picture find the closest color from a limited set Introducing plastic bird, our subject of study.
I want to extract the color from image at position x:0 and y:0.</description></item></channel></rss>